

#### **ABOUT ME**

29 years old and living in 2600, Glostrup

Links to website, LinkedIn and contact:

www.olivereierstrand.dk

LinkedIn

mreierstrand@hotmail.com +4540475805

School and leisure projects, including my own personal portfolio, can be found on my website.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML - CSS - TailwindCSS -Bootstrap - JavaScript - Vue.js -Svelte - Docker - Accessibility -UI/UX udvikling

#### **EDUCATION**

**Computer Science** 2019-2021

Erhvervsakademi Zealand Roskilde

2011-2014

Kongsholm Gymnasium & HF Albertslund

# OLIVER EIERSTRAND

# Frontend- & web developer

#### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

With more than 1.5 years of experience in modern front-end technologies such as Vue.js, JavaScript, CSS and HTML, I have developed several user-friendly and intuitive user experiences. I am highly detail-oriented, eager to learn, enterprising and curious. These characteristics have helped me to have a strong detail-oriented approach to UI/UX design and developing and improving user-friendly interfaces.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Frontend Developer

# April 2022 - January 2023

# Magenta

- · Handling all front-end related tasks in Magenta, as well as guiding other developers in the company.
- Lead the development of a cross-functional design system for Magenta products.
- Lead a frontend experience group to share frontend knowledge, improve frontend work across Magenta projects, and set direction for frontend work in the different teams in Magenta.
- Lead the planning of, work distribution during, and follow-up on a frontend workshop to rewrite Magenta's largest project: OS2MO's frontend from Vue-js to Svelte.
- Lead the development of a new Svelte frontend for OS2MO. Including:
  - Brainstorming and developing a new Design System for OS2MO before the new frontend was implemented.
- · Creating mockups and prototypes in Figma.
- Improve UI and UX in OS2MO to make OS2MO more user-friendly and intuitive.
- Taking care of everything related to Accessibility in design in Magenta projects.

# Frontend Internship

#### October 2021 - November 2021

#### Lasso X

- Participated in an internship at Lasso X to strengthen skills in front-end development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vue.js).
- Created a "Meet our customers" subpage with videos, testimonials and a contact form.
- Improved existing code and features in the Lasso portal and added new functionality to Lasso X's product.
- Expanded my skills in front-end development and UI/UX in collaboration with the Design department at Lasso.

#### Computer Science Internship

# January 2021 - April 2021

#### MeeW

- · Participated in an internship at MeeW on a customer-related project developed in React Native.
- Acquired skills in React Native development.
- Understood the importance of customer contact and relationship before, during and after the development phase.